[{"answer": "Good so far.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "First of all, I did a lot of praying.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "When you hear that video and you realize that that was the moment that you were saved, how does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Did you feel that there was no chance you would be saved?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Thank you very much.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "How you doing?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "First of all, I'd like to say I'm glad that the Lord was -- had them there at that time to spare my life, and I'm very, very thankful for them, and I wish them the very best of luck and I'm hoping that maybe in the future here, the future will look good for them, too, as for me.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "And, Alex, how do you feel about these two men who probably saved your life?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "It's kind of breathtaking.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "When you look at it, how does it make you feel?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "She's good.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "How is she, first of all?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I just threw my car and park as fast as I could and just ran to her school as fast as I could run.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What did you do?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "When you think back to the moment that you saw the school had gone, you must have feared the absolute worst, didn't you?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I was the first one to climb out.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "What were you thinking as you saw the devastation?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "People -- when the responders started coming in, they told us that her school wasn't hit, and I was grateful to know that she was OK because before it hit she said mom, just go get safe, I'm safe.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "How quickly was it that you discovered she was OK?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "It took me about two hours to get to her.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "When could you talk to her?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "This is Kaylie.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "And what's your daughter's name, Jamie?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "With lots of prayer and support.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "How are you bearing up with this?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "AVIS: Well, I tried to leave my work and I was about -- probably about 20 minutes away and the sirens went off at my work and I was unable to leave.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "But when you heard about the tornado striking and realized how powerful it was, where were you and how quickly could you get to the school?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "He was an outstanding child.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "What kind of boy was he?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "You know, I was told that the kids in the third and second grade building where did exactly what they had been trained to do and I know the schools did what -- they did everything that they were supposed to do.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "And what do you think should happen?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "The husband and the son are really surrounded and insulated by a number of friends and family members, lifetime friends, and they've done a great job of caring for them and helping them walk through the process, making the decisions they've had to make.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "How are they doing?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Great question.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "How do you go about consoling people in this sort of situation?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Is this your true verdict, so say you one and all?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "It feels great.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "When you're back down there now, how does it seem to you in terms of its recovery?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Well, I would just advise the people who have been affected to just stick together.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Michael, when you look at what's happened in Oklahoma, the devastating tornado there, another place that now has to try and rebuild exactly as where you are now had to, what is the best advice you would give to those people?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, it's a catastrophic event and certainly emotions run high.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What are the most important things, do you think, when these kind of things happen that you have to deal with?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Did you feel that you got enough help from federal and state level after Sandy?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "So Atlantic City is back in business, is it, for Memorial Weekend?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "We're looking great.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "You going to be at the Superbowl this year?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Piers, basically I agree with a lot of what the president's done in recent years, but the tone of today's speech I just thought was wrong.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "What is your reaction to the president's speech today?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, one of the major developments today was the revelation that one of those that were arrested and that perpetrated this attack attended meetings of a pro- al Qaeda support group here in the United Kingdom.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What do we know about these men?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Now, the suspect that we saw giving his extraordinary interview clutching the machete, he's been identified as Michael Adabalago (ph)?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "That's absolutely right, that he was the suspect that attended these rallies.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "And is he the suspect you were talking about just then, who had attended these rallies?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, they're very worried, indeed, Piers.", "docId": "130523pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "How worried are the authorities about more of this happening?", "qSentId": 501}]